NETFLIX オリジナルシリーズ
〜
This Yanagawara Camp
（雄哉(ゆうや)）この柳河原(やながわら)キャンプは
is used as CAAC Special Forces' base
対策庁の特務編成部隊が
エリア内に侵入する際
起点とした施設だ
whenever they enter the Area.
The Guillotine Shutter's electric shock
ギロチン･シャッターの
電撃の影響で
has paralyzed the Matter in this area.
ここ一帯のマターは麻痺(まひ)している
しばらくは 大丈夫だ
It will be safe for now.
（アイコ）あっ…
（楓(かえで)）えっ？ 正面から入れんの？
What? We can enter through the front?
（篠山(しのやま)）
ここに来るのも 久しぶりだな
I haven't been here in a while.
That's true.
（白石(しらいし)）そうね
Who the heck is that guy anyway?
（一樹(かずき)）あの人 何者(なにもん)ですかね？
（相模(さがみ)）さあな
I don't know.
ん？
External insulation and circulation
systems checked.
（篠山）
外界からの隔離も
閉鎖循環系も問題ない
We can relax here for a bit.
いっときの羽伸ばしだ
（白石）スーツ 脱げるわよ
You can take off your suit.
There's showers here.
こっちにシャワーがあるわ
Yahoo!
（楓）きゃっほ〜！
ライブスーツ お願い 遙香(はるか)！
Watch my Live Suit, Haruka!
Hey! Kaede!
（遙香）ちょっと 楓！
（一樹）うわっ…
I tried, but I can't get it off.
（アイコ）
やってみたんですけど
脱げなくて…
（遙香）
セパレータは作動してるのに
The separator has been activated,
so the Live Suit must have
high affinity with your skin.
あなたの肌って
ライブスーツと親和性が高いのね
Really? Is that so?
えっ？ そっ そうなんですか？
（白石）
スーツに好かれちゃったみたいね
I guess your suit is pretty fond of you.
That is everyone's duties.
（篠山）作業の割り当ては以上だ
なお これ以降
補給可能なポイントはない
There are no more resupply points ahead.
積み残し等 ないよう
Ensure you're well supplied.
（相模）うっす
（遙香）はい
-Got it.
-Yessir.
Minase, you're on guard duty.
（篠山）水瀬(みなせ)は周辺警戒を頼む
（一樹）ああ はい！
Yes, sir.
-Excuse me.
-What?
（アイコ）あの…
（一同）ん？
Can I accompany him?
私も ついて行っていいですか？
（一同）え？
一度 ちゃんと見ておきたくて
エリアの様子
I want to get a good look at the Area.
It's not safe!
絶対に安全ってわけじゃ…
Join me!
（一樹）行こうよ！
俺がボディガードするよ
I'll be your bodyguard.
ありがとう
Thank you.
But...
いや しかし…
From what our sensors tell us,
this area is secure right now.
（一樹）
計測数値的には 今 この周辺域は
安全が確保されてる
その程度の判断
If you're leading us
to Primary Point, you should
be able to make a call like that.
プライマリー･ポイントまでの
案内人なら できると思うけど？
（雄哉 ため息）
（白石）さ〜て 働いてもらうわよ
All right, we're going to need you now.
（カチッ）
（黒瀬(くろせ)）人型？
In human form?
（雄哉）
先日の大活性が
マターの異変を招いたのか？
Maybe the activity the other day
transformed the Matter.
Or the transformation itself
caused the activity.
それとも マターの異変そのものが
大活性の原因か？
（黒瀬）
ともあれ こっちからも
できるかぎりサポートする
Anyway, I'll do what I can
to support you from here.
（雄哉）お願いします
-Thanks.
-Besides,
な〜に
I was supposed to go to Tokyo,
but this makes things easier.
東京に出向くつもりだったが
手間が省けた
I'll pay her a visit.
ちょいと 彼女に会ってくる
（南原(なんばら)）
とにかく そっちは堀(ほり)に任せたから
At any rate, I'll keep Hori in charge.
永田町(ながたちょう)周りに動きがあったら
逐次 報告入れて
Keep me informed of what
happens in the capital.
Bye.
じゃあ
（黒瀬）
お待ちしておりました
南原課長
I'm your ride, Superintendent Nanbara.
迎えは必要ないと お伝え…
I told them I didn't need a...
Sorry, you're a director now, right?
失礼 今は局長だったか？
あっ… 黒瀬君
Kurose?
（アイコ）知りませんでした
I didn't know that Divers have
such an amazing job.
ダイバーの皆さんが
こんな すごい仕事されてるって
No, it's not as amazing
as you think, Tachibana.
（一樹）
いや〜 それほどでもないよ
橘(たちばな)さん
（アイコ）あっ アイコでいいです
Call me Aiko.
Then call me Kazuki.
（一樹）じゃあ 俺も一樹で
-Aiko...
-Yes?
（一樹）アイコ… ちゃん
（アイコ）ん？
So...
その…
ああ そう！
Ｋ１で言ってたよね？
What was it you said at K1?
家族のために
You need to get to Primary Point
to save your family? Is that true?
プライマリー･ポイントに
行かなきゃって
あれって…
あっ…
（ため息）
あっ 何か悪いこと…
Did I say too much?
ううん ごめんなさい…
No. I'm sorry.
Well, it's really quiet.
（楓）へえ 静かだね〜
（一樹）あっ
やっぱ ギロチンの威力
ハンパないなあ
That Guillotine sure is powerful.
（一樹）なんで…
Why are you here?
（楓）
あんただけじゃ心配だから
わざわざ 来てあげたんじゃない
I was worried about you alone,
so I came to help.
Aren't you and Seri
supposed to be resupplying?
お前は芹(せり)さんと一緒に
補充担当だろ？
I get a lot more work done
without Kaede around.
やっぱり 楓がいないと
はかどるわね
Look at all this.
にしても 急ごしらえとはいえ
さすがは政府の施設
The government can do amazing things,
even in a hurry.
These resources are incredible
すごい ストックだわ
Hydro, okay.
（白石）ハイドロもオッケーっと
It's in pretty good shape
for being abandoned.
置き去りにしたわりには
状態よくって助かった
（ノック）
（白石）どうぞ
Come in.
You know...
まったく…
I'm amazed you're
carrying out this bold plan,
よくもまあ こんな大胆な作戦
やろうと思ったもんだわ
神崎(かんざき)雄哉君
Yuya Kanzaki.
白石さんの協力がなかったら
成立しませんでしたよ
I never could have done it
without your cooperation.
（南原）相変わらず 鼻が利くわね
As always, you have keen intuition.
This is good timing.
Aiko Tachibana has gone missing.
ちょうど よかった
橘アイコが失踪したそうね
（黒瀬）情報が早いな
You already know about it?
おかげで 院内は上を下へだよ
It has sent the hospital into a flurry.
Do you know anything?
何か知ってる？
（黒瀬）皆目
（南原）そう
-No.
-I see.
You must know something.
君のほうこそ 何か…
It's green.
青！
Oh, no!
（黒瀬）おっと！
You can tell me. We're still friends,
even though you dumped me in college.
学生時代に フラれたよしみだ
俺にも聞かせてもらえるか？
Are you here to deal with
the Matter's activity these past few days?
こっちへ来たのは
このあいだからの
マター大活性の対処か？
Yes.
ええ
But you can easily give orders from Tokyo.
なら 東京からでも
指示が出せるだろ？
What is the real reason you're here?
本当は何なんだ？
No way!
（楓）何それ？
Your dad died in an accident,
父親が事故で死んで
母親と弟がバーストで行方不明って
and your mom and brother went missing
in the Burst?
That's crazy!
すっごいね！
Hey!
（一樹）おい！
But you're going to save them?
You really think they're still alive?
（楓）
でも 助けに行くって
生きてんの ホントに？
（一樹）ああ…
Jeez! You're so damn insensitive!
ったく デリカシーないヤツだな！
（楓）ふん！
この川には…
This river...
ここにあった川の上流には
よく 家族で来てたんです
My family often used to visit
the upper end of this river.
お父さんが釣りが好きで
小(ち)っちゃい頃は
Dad loved fishing.
When I was little,
私も家族と一緒にいるのが
楽しかったから
I really enjoyed spending time
with my family,
so I came with him.
喜んで ついてきてた
けど だんだんと そういうの
煩わしくなってきちゃって
But I slowly got annoyed
at those kind of things.
そのうち
お父さんも仕事が忙しくなって
Also, Dad got so busy with work
that he hardly ever came home.
あんまり
家に帰ってこれなくなって…
でもね たまに帰ってくると言うの
But when he did come home, he would say,
アイコ 釣りに行こうって
"Let's go fishing, Aiko.
お母さんと亮太(りょうた)と…
Me, you, Mom, and Ryota,
家族みんなで
デッカいのを釣りに行こうって
let's all go and catch a big one."
そんなの
一度も釣れたことないのに
We never caught any big fish.
今 思えば お父さんなりに
When I think about it now,
I realize that
he was trying to make time
with his family in his own way.
家族と一緒に過ごす時間
作ろうとしてたんだなって
でも 不器用だから
But since he wasn't very social,
that was all he could think of doing.
他に
思いつかなかったんだろうなって
It's too late now
to start wishing we could be together.
今更だよね
一緒にいたくなるなんて
大切だったんだってことに
やっと 気付くなんて
It's sad I only just realized
how important they are to me.
はあ？ 大切？ 家族が？
What? Important? Family?
Of course! You have...
（一樹）
何言ってんだよ！ お前だって…
No, I don't!
（楓）いないし！ そんなの
生まれたときには
もう 父親いなかったし
When I was born, my dad was already gone.
母親は私が生まれたの きっかけに
新しい男と逃げてったし
After I was born, my mom seized her chance
to run away with another guy.
I was left behind and passed around
my relatives.
残されたこっちは
親戚じゅう たらい回し
I feel relieved now that I'm alone.
１人になって
私は せいせいしてるけど
That's your family, though!
（一樹）
それは お前んちの話だろ！
あんただって逃げてきたんでしょ？
家族から
You ran away from your own family, right?
あっ…
（楓）タウンじゃ有名
Everyone in Town knows
どっかのお坊ちゃんが
冷やかしに来たって
you're a spoiled rich kid
who needed an escape.
（一樹）そんなんじゃ…
That's not true!
俺は… 自分で
生き方 決めたいって思っただけだ
All I wanted was to decide
how to live my own life!
I was sick of people bragging about
happiness and misfortune!
他人の幸せ自慢も不幸自慢も
飽き飽きしたんだよ！
それを冷やかしって言うんだけど
That's what an escape is.
I had an arm eaten off by Matter
and got an artificial organism arm!
こっちはマターに食われて
腕１本 人工生体に替えてるんだ！
言ってるそばから 不幸自慢？
ダッサ！
Who's bragging
about misfortune now, loser?
You special ordered a new arm
made from artificial organisms!
義手１本 丸ごと人工生体で
特注できるって
You're still a spoiled rich kid!
お坊ちゃんってことじゃん！
Having fun out here?
（相模）にぎやかだな
Quit fighting and get some rest.
ダベってねえで
カラダは休めておけ
Sagami...
（一樹）相模さん…
Stay on your guard.
（相模）気 引き締めていけよ
Right now, who knows
what might happen inside the Area?
エリアん中は 今
何が起こってもおかしくねえんだ
（南原）
結局 現場に来ないと
分からないことだらけ
You can't know what's going on
until you're on-site.
But without going inside the Area,
まあ エリアに入れない以上
得られる情報は限られてるけど
the information we can get is limited.
Aren't you sending in a recon team?
調査隊を入れたりしないのか？
The Area is completely
sealed off now.
エリアは現在 絶対封鎖よ
何人(なんぴと)たりとも
入ることはできないわ
Not a single person can get in.
何人たりとも… ねえ
Not a single person, huh?
It looks like the neutralizer
you injected Aiko with is working.
（白石）
アイコちゃんに投与した中和剤
ちゃんと 機能してるみたいね
Make sure the Divers don't find out.
くれぐれも みんなに悟られないで
生身と人工生体との合成体が
発する生理活性物質が
Most Divers know Matter is attracted
to biologically active substances
excreted by a composite
マターを引き寄せることは
ダイバー界では周知の事実よ
of real and artificial organisms.
言われるまでもない
I know that much.
（白石）１つ 聞いてもいい？
Can I ask you something?
あなたは そもそも マターが
どうして発生したと考えてるの？
How do you think the Matter was created?
Aiko Tachibana was in an accident.
The treatment that split her
事故に遭った橘アイコに
施した分離治療が
複製体の人工生体細胞の
異常増殖を引き起こした
set off abnormal artificial cell
proliferation in the duplicate body.
今 はっきり言えるのは
それだけだ
That's all I can say for certain.
What was the cause?
理由は？
Was it a warning
not to attempt something taboo?
禁忌を犯そうとする者に対する
警告？
禁忌も警告も関係ない
It has nothing to do with any of that.
人工生体に関する想定が未熟だった
というだけだ
We simply didn't know enough
about what artificial organisms could do.
You mean even Toshihide Yura
didn't know enough?
由良俊英(ゆらとしひで)にも
そんな未熟さがあったと？
そういうことだ
That's what I'm saying.
で 生み出されたもう１人の彼女は
どうするつもり？
So, what are you going to do
with her fake body?
あるべきところに帰す
Return it where it belongs.
勝手に生み落としておいて？
And let his creation live?
それで 由良の罪が
本当につぐなえると？
Will that atone
for the sin Yura committed?
（雄哉）心配はいらない
Don't worry about that.
たとえ その原因が未知だとしても
Even if we don't know the cause,
putting things back the way they were
is a simple process.
元に戻すプロセスそのものは
シンプルだ
実地に近いシミュレーションも…
Simulations show...
I'm not asking that.
（白石）そういうことじゃない
Her brain and body
function just like a real person.
脳も体も人と同様 機能してるのよ
生み出されたもう１人の彼女が
人間でないと言い切れるの？
Can you really say that
her replica is not human?
She is clearly not human.
人間でないことは明白だ
彼女は単なる…
（ノック）
She's no more than...
I've finished refitting
the Bipod batteries.
（篠山）
バイポッドのバッテリーの換装は
終わった
Daisuke.
（白石）大輔(だいすけ)…
I'll have everyone load all
the vial cartridges in here later.
（篠山）
バイアルカートリッジは
あとで 全員でこっちに積み込む
これから先
マターの活性度は どんどん上がる
From here on,
Matter activity will continue to rise.
Even so, do you still want to go?
それでも… 行くんだな？
（一樹）あのさ〜 何者？
So, who is he?
What?
はっ？
（一樹）神崎雄哉って…
Who is Yuya Kanzaki?
-A classmate.
-A classmate?
（アイコ）同級生…
（一樹）同級生？
Actually, I don't know him that well.
（アイコ）
っていうか 私もよく知らなくて…
Really?
（一樹）えっ？
He transferred just before summer break.
（アイコ）
夏休み直前に転校してきて
そこで 初めて知り合って…
That's when I first met him.
I was brought to you guys
right after that,
すぐに
みんなのところに連れてこられて
and now we're all going to Primary Point.
プライマリー･ポイントに
行くことになっちゃって
What? Are you kidding?
That's totally fishy!
ちょっ 何それ？ 超怪しいじゃん！
Why go to such a dangerous place with him?
そんなので あんな危険な所に？
なんで？
あっ…
（相模）一樹！
（一樹）あっ…
Kazuki!
Divers never get involved in
their client's business.
（楓）
ダイバーは
クライアントの事情に深入りしない
んなの分かってるけど
今度のは ただの回収とは…
I know that!
But this isn't a normal retrieval!
It's exactly the same.
Isn't that right, client?
同じだ
だよな？ クライアントさん
（一同）ん？
Shinoyama said to move
（雄哉）
篠山さんがバイポッドの私物を
ビートルに移動させるようにと
all personal belongings
from the Bipods to the Beetle,
相模さんには１時間後に警戒を交代
とのことです
and he'll be taking over guard duty
for Sagami in one hour.
（南原）
送ってくれたお礼に忠告しとく
As a thank you,
I'll give you a warning.
Don't get any more involved with
what's happening in the Area.
これ以上 エリア内のことには
関わらないほうがいいわ
（車のドア閉まる）
これからもずっと
いい友達でいたいから
You see, I'd like to remain
good friends forever.
Bye.
じゃ
何か ろくに中身見ないまま
持ってきちゃった
I hardly looked inside
before bringing this.
SUMMER NOTEBOOK TWO
バッカ…
I'm such an idiot.
ん？
Oh, this is...
あっ… これって…
（アイコの父）
誕生日おめでとう
Happy birthday.
Do you want some help, Aiko?
（一樹）アイコちゃん
手伝おうか？
（アイコ）え？
I'm okay!
あっ！ 大丈夫！
（アイコ）ああ〜っ！
（一樹）え？え？え？
うわっ！
What?
えっ？
-What?
-What happened?
（一樹）うわっ！
（楓）え？ 何！
What is it?
何？
Unidentified living organism detected
in North Block storage area.
（アナウンス）
北ブロック 格納区画にて
入構登録のない生物体を
感知しました
繰り返します…
I repeat...
（篠山）何があった！
What happened?
あっ…
（２人）あっ…
（カチッ）
（青い生体）キュー
What?
（アイコ）へっ？
キュイ？
（遙香）ホロス･ハビリスが
That's a sample organism that
Holos Habilis gave to a few customers.
一部の顧客だけに配布した
サンプル生体よ
Holos Habilis?
That's the company Dad worked for.
（アイコ）
ホロス･ハビリス
お父さんが勤めてた会社…
So, this thing is yours, Aiko?
じゃあ こいつ アイコちゃんの？
But when I dropped it, it was just a ball.
でも 私が落としたのって
こんな まんまるい…
It was in storage mode.
保管形態ね
Did the electric shock wake you up?
あんた 感電して目が覚めたの？
Must be an exposed wire.
漏電か
It's from your dad?
お父さんから？
はい 誕生日のプレゼントに
Yes. It was a birthday present.
But the accident happened
right after that,
でも… もらった直後に
事故に遭っちゃったから
結局 それが何か知らないままで…
so I never found out what it was.
（楓）ねえ ねえ！
Hey!
（楓）名前 なんての？
（アイコ）えっ？
-What's its name?
-Huh?
Doesn't have one?
ないの？
I just found out it's a living creature.
っていうか
生き物だったなんていうのも
今 知ったので…
とても価値のあるものよ
It's very valuable.
ホロスタイプ…
This Holos type is an artificially created
complete living organism.
ひとつの個体
丸ごとの人工生体なんて
What?
Its whole body is an artificial organism?
えっ？ 体全部が人工生体…
バーストで
開発が中止になったものだ
Its development was suspended
after the Burst.
こんな試作品があったとは…
I didn't know there were prototypes.
（アイコ）私の体って
My body
ライブスーツとか この動物と
同じものでできてるんだよね？
is made of the same stuff as the Live Suit
and this animal, right?
Yes.
（雄哉）ああ
Since your whole body is
made from artificial organisms,
全身が人工生体で作られている
という点において
そのサンプルも 君も
極めて貴重な存在だ
both you and that sample
are extremely precious.
You make us sound like objects.
何か 物みたいな言い方…
You are.
（雄哉）物だよ
No, to be more precise,
いや 正確に言うなら
you're a system
for artificially creating life.
生命現象を
人工的に生み出すためのシステムだ
そんなこと言ってるんじゃない
That's not what I meant.
でも 事実だ
But it's the truth.
The system that gives you life
今 君を生かしている
そのシステムは
is something humans
have wanted a long time.
人が ずっと手にしたいと
願っていたものなんだよ
Stop it!
（アイコ）やめてよ！
（青い生体）キュー
You don't understand, Kanzaki!
神崎君には
きっと 分かんないんだよね！
あっ…
Um...
ああっと…
そろそろ 相模と交代なんだが
I'll be taking over for Sagami soon,
ライブスーツのメンテが
済んでるようだったら…
so if you're done
with the Live Suit repairs...
It can't be.
（アイコ）そんなの…
Nobody wants their body
to be like a monster.
誰も お化けみたいな体にして
なんて頼んでないよ
（青い生体）キュキュ…
キュキュキュ
キュキュキュ…
あっ！
（アイコ）プレゼント？
A present?
（南原）桐生(きりゅう)先生に代わって
If Kurose takes over
as the company head after Dr. Kiryu,
黒瀬君が
代表に立つようなことがあったら
he's sure to stop
Cell Assembler Two research
彼は このまま
バーストが終息するまで
セル･アセンブラ２(ツー)の研究を
中断するでしょうね
until the Burst is brought to an end.
I won't allow this country's economy
to be ruined any more.
これ以上
この国の経済を
疲弊させるわけにはいかないわ
I agree with you.
（伊佐津）私も思いは同じだ
この桐生研は
さらなる歩みを止めるべきではない
We shouldn't slow the progress
of Kiryu Research.
So, I'm doing something about it.
なに… 手は打ってある
（相模）ダメだ！
（楓）見つかんない！
-No luck!
-I can't find her!
Why did you leave her alone?
（一樹）なんで１人にしたんだよ！
This is bad!
A contamination suit is gone.
（遙香）
まずいわ！ 防護服が１つない！
-What?
Matter activity detected near facility.
（アナウンス）
施設付近に
マターの活性反応を確認しました
私たちも！
大輔にも伝えないと！
We have to do something.
I have to tell Daisuke.
Hey! Where are you?
（アイコ）お〜い！ どこ〜？
Where are you?
どこにいるの〜？
（青い生体）キュキュ…
（アイコ）あっ…
Hey! Where did you go?
お〜い！ どこ行っちゃったの〜！
うわっ！ きゃあ〜！
Where are you, Tachibana?
（雄哉）どこだ！ 橘！
That doesn't hurt.
（アイコ）痛… くない
だよね…
Of course not.
I was saved by the same stuff
that little guy is made of.
私 あの子たちを生み出した力で
助けてもらったんだよね
もし そうじゃなかったら…
If not, then I'd be...
Where am I?
ここ どこだろう？
（カサッ）
あっ…
No, I still haven't found her.
I'll look a little...
いや まだ見つからない
もう少し 範囲を…
おっ…
Even if it's safe around here,
you can't go out on your own.
（篠山）
いくら安全な状況とはいえ
１人で出歩かれちゃ―
こっちは いくつ命があっても
足りなくなる
We don't want to risk lives over this.
（アイコ）すみません
I'm sorry.
I admit you're pretty brave.
（篠山）しかし えらい覚悟だ
ダイバーでも
近づこうとしない場所へ
You're going to a place
most Divers would never come close to.
君は向かおうをしている
So, you should understand him.
なら 分かるはずだ
彼もまた君と同じように
Like you, he's doing his best
大きな何かを背負い
這い進もうとしている
to move on with life
while carrying a huge burden.
得体の知れないヤツだが
We may not know who he is,
but you can at least understand
that much about him.
それだけは
分かってやってもいいかもな
ん…
（柚葉(ゆずは)）あっ！ 雷鳥！
It's a snow grouse!
Oh, Dad! Don't film me!
Film the snow grouse!
もう お父さん！
私はいいから 雷鳥撮ってよ！
お父さんってば！
Give it to me, Dad!
Today, Dr. Yura, Dad, and I came
to Murodo together.
今日は室堂(むろどう)に 由良先生と
お父さんと柚葉の３人で来ました！
Dr. Yura, do you like the lunch
that I made?
（柚葉）
ねえ 由良先生
私の作ったお弁当 おいしい？
I knew you'd like it!
でしょ！
Maybe I'll become your wife one day..
柚葉 由良先生の奥さんに
なってあげよっかな！
Yuzuha.
柚葉…
Even Yura couldn't bring you
out of your coma.
あの由良にも
お前を目覚めさせることは
できなかったんだ
All that stuff about the Yura Notes
must be a lie.
由良ノートなどというものも
きっと まやかしだ
お前は お父さんが必ず…
As your father,
I promise to bring you back.
Aiko!
（一樹）アイコちゃん！
I'm very sorry, everyone.
皆さん すみませんでした
Well, at least we found you.
（相模）まっ 見つかって何よりだ
Be more careful!
It's not just your life at risk.
（楓）
気をつけてよね
あんた一人の命じゃないんだから
Hey!
（一樹）お前！
あっ 神崎君は？
Where is Kanzaki?
You found her?
（雄哉）無事だったか！
ハア ハア… よかった
Thank goodness.
ハア ハア…
ごめんなさい　私が…
I'm sorry. If I...
私が死んじゃったら…
If I died...
I wouldn't be able to save
Mom and Ryota, would I?
お母さんと亮太を
助けに行けなくなるんだもんね
こうして生きてるから
助けに行けるんだもんね
I can only save them if I'm still alive.
（青い生体）キュウ
This is precious, right?
（雄哉）大切なものだろ？
キュウ！
うん！
Yes.
ごめんね
I'm sorry.
神崎君 ありがとう
Thank you, Kanzaki.
ねえ グミはちゃんと乗ってる？
Hey, is Gummi on board?
Gummi?
グミ？
（楓）
その子の名前！
お菓子のグミみたいだから
That's its name
because it's like gummy candy.
おいしそうじゃん！
Looks yummy, no?
So random...
（一樹）んな適当な…
-I like it!
-You do?
（アイコ）うん！ いい！
（遙香）いいんだ…
It's cute!
かわいい！
I told you.
（楓）でしょ！
（グミ）キュイ
（篠山）どうやら 夜更けの警報は
Last night's alarm
was because Matter activity
was detected near K2.
Ｋ２付近での
マターの活性を感知したものらしい
（一樹）
ここまで 届いたんですか？
It's gotten this far?
It must be up to the K2 gate.
We can't let our guard down.
（相模）
Ｋ２の門番に違いない
やっぱり 油断ならねえな
（白石）みんな 準備はいい？
Is everyone ready?
-Wilco!
（一同）ウィルコー！
Here we go!
出すわよ！
（警備員）特別通達の車両が
Special comms vehicles
have just passed through Aimoto Dam
and entered Area One.
今 愛本遮断堰(あいもとしゃだんぜき)を通過
エリア１に入りました
（南原）了解　ご苦労さまです
I got it. Thank you.
Today's topic is a breach of trust
by Susumu Kurose,
（竹原(たけはら)）
本日の議題は 黒瀬研究室主任
head of the Kurose Research Lab.
黒瀬進(すすむ)医師の背任
特別予算着服ならびに
業務上横領についてとなります
He is accused of misappropriation of funds
and corporate embezzlement.
Then, let us begin.
では… 始めましょう
〜
Subtitle translation by Brian Athey